[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_BS",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M1_BS_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock&&16_BSMSQ_19",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M1_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M1_Vector_Start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M1_Vector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M1_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_EG",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M1_EG_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M1_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M1_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M1_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_SM",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M1_SM_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M1_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M1_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M1_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_RW",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M1_RW_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M1_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M1_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M1_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M2_FindOakes",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 62,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M2_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M2_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionFamilyWardAngryEarthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M2_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M2_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M2_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M2_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M2_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M3_EnterJungle",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 63,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Hargest_NE_C",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M2",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M3_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M3_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M3_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M3_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M3_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M3_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M4_ReachSettlement",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 63,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Riches_M5",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M4",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M3",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M4_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M4_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M4_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M4_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M4_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M4_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M5_DefendSettlement",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 64,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Riches_M5",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M5",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M4",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M5_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M5_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M5_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M5_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M5_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M5_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M6_FindKim",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 63,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kim",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M6",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M6_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M6_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M6_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M6_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M6_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M7_ExtractKim",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kim_SC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M7",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M6",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M7_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M7_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M7_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M7_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M7_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M7_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M8_MeetTaurus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 61,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M8_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Taurus",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M8",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M7",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M8_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M8_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M8_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M8_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M8_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M8_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M8_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M9_MeetShirzad",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M9_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Shirzad",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M9",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M8",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M9_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M9_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M9_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M9_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M9_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M9_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M9_Completed_A",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M10_MeetKurok",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M10_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kurok",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M9",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M10_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "BananaT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M10_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M10_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M10_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M10_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M10_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M10_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M11_FightMahantaram",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M11_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M10",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M11_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M11_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M11_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M11_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M11_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M11_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M11_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M12_FightMedusa",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M12_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_HG",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M11",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M12_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M12_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M12_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M12_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M12_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M12_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M12_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M13_AttuneStaff",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M13_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_SE",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M12",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M13_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "09A_M11_CraftingMatsBox",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M13_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M13_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M13_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M13_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M13_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M13_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M14_GetInfusedSeed",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M14_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_LC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M13",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M14_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M14_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M14_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M14_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M14_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M14_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M14_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_M15_FightArtemis",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_M15_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_End",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M14",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M15_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Artifact_Set1_MediumLegs",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_M15_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_M15_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_M15_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_M15_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_M15_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_M15_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S0_SecretoftheSpores",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S0_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Eldred",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S0_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S0_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "SporeJellyT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S0_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S0_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S0_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S0_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S0_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S0_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S1_SaveAnimals",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 62,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Murrow_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S1",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "BeastSporesT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S1_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S1_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S1_Completed",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S3_HuntHercyne",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 62,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Vachon_WC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S3_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S3_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S3_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S3_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S3_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S3_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S4_BlowUpFarm",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 63,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S4_Container_Main",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S4",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M3",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S4_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "AngryEarthSporesT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S4_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S4_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S4_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S4_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S4_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S5_SavePrivateer",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 64,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_James",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S5",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M4",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S5_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S5_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S5_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S5_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S5_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S5_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S6_TrackBeasts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 64,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Fionn_SC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S6",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S6_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S6_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S6_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S6_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S6_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S7_StopPlague",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 64,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Ramla",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S7",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S7_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "AncientSporesT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S7_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S7_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S7_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S7_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S7_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S8_FixAncientWiring",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S8_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Josephine",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S8_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S8_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S8_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S8_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S8_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S8_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S8_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S9_HackDefenses",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S9_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kievan",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S9",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_S7",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S9_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PetrifiedFragmentsT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S9_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S9_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S9_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S9_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S9_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S9_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S10_FindTaurusRelics",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 61,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S10_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Marwa",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M7",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S10_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "BeastSporesT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S10_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S10_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S10_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S10_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S10_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S10_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S11_BeatTimeTrial",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S11_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Marwa_HHOP",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S11_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S11_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S11_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S11_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S11_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S11_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S11_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S12_TraverseLionCave",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S12_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Shirzad",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S12_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S12_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S12_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S12_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S12_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S12_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S12_Completed",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S13_FightLizardAvatar",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S13_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Barug",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S13_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S13_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S13_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S13_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S13_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S13_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S13_Completed",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S14_FightEliteBeasts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S14_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Manmosu_SD",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S14_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S14_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S14_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S14_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S14_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S14_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S14_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S15_ResearchDarkMagic",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S15_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Johannes",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S15_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "UnpetrifiedFleshT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S15_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S15_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S15_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S15_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S15_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S15_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S16_DestroyAbomination",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S16_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Johannes",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S16_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PetrifiedFragmentsT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S16_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S16_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S16_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S16_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S16_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S16_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S17_EstablishDefenses",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S17_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Hargest_LC",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M14",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S17_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "AngryEarthSporesT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S17_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S17_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S17_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S17_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S17_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S17_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S18_ScanElafryMagic",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S18_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Gauss",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S18_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 4,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S18_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S18_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S18_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S18_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S18_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S18_Completed",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S20_DefeatBeastLords",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S20_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Manmosu_SD",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_S14",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S20_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S20_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S20_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S20_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S20_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S20_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S20_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S21_AmongStatues",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S21_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_EdithShackleton_end",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S8",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M11",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S21_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@09A_S21_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S21_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S21_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S21_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S21_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S21_Completed_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "09A_S19_DestroyBadPlants_v2",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "09A_S19_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_SD_2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "09A_S19",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S19_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@09A_S19_Title",
		"Description": "@09A_S19_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@09A_S19_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@09A_S19_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@09A_S19_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@09A_S19_Completed_a",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@09A_S19_Cooldown",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	}
]